记时器
不管你的计算机是否已准备好
离2000年只剩余318天
Whether your computers ready or not,
there are only 318 days till the year 2000.
A group of corporations concerned about the problems
一群担心千年虫计算机危机的公司
已经召集会议…
related to the Y2K computer bug have convened...
1999年2月20日
乖，不要哭
No. Dont cry.
别哭，嘿
Dont cry. Hey.
没事了
Everythings gonna be okay.
嗨，没事了
Hi. Everythings gonna be okay, pal.
来，对
Come here, come here. Yeah.
乖宝宝，好，不哭了
Thats a good boy. Okay, dont cry.
她不会再伤害你了
She cant hurt you anymore.
都结束了，来 没有人能够再伤害你了
Its over. Come here. No ones gonna hurt you ever again.
乔的酒吧 成立于1948年
2011年4月17日
我是刘易斯希克斯 我是个采访记者
My name is Louis Hicks. Im an investigative reporter.
专门采访杀人犯及罪犯的故事
I cover stories of killers and criminals.
他们的人生是黑暗 毫无希望的
Their lives are dark, without hope.
我试着不受其影响，但很难
I try not to let it affect me, but its hard.
一嘿！高登！暍两杯 一不行！
-Hey! Gordo! Two shots. -No!
一好啦 一不行、不行
-Yes, yes. -No, no, no, no.
一我一小时后上班 －一杯
-I got to work in an hour. -Just one, just one.
一不行 －一杯，传统方式
-No, no. -One shot, old-school.
一杯，就一杯 一好啦
-One. One shot. -There it is.
一敬刘易斯 一对
-To Louis. -Yeah.
好，现在你请了我 换我请你吃早餐
All right, now you do something for me.
Let me buy you breakfast.
太晚了，我已经吃过了 冠军的早餐
Too late. I already ate. Breakfast of champions.
工作还好吗？有任何令人注目
我该知道的真人实事吗？
Hows work? Any compelling
real-life stories I should know about?
今天没有
Not today.
男砖
Well
你呢？ 在写书了吗？
Hows work for you, huh? You working on the book?
一直都在写啊，高登
Always. Always working, Gordo.